Guide to the Laura (Riding) Jackson and Schuyler B. Jackson collection, 1924-1991
Jackson, Laura (Riding) and Schuyler B., 1924-1991
- Series III. Correspondence
  - A) Laura (Riding) Jackson
    - Incoming
      - Ohannessian, Griselda, See: Series III. Correspondence C)Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Griselda Ohannessian (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - O'Haire, Moran, Apr. 10, 1980-1986 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Oldham, James, Jan. 19-Feb. 18, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Oliver, Peter and Mary, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Mary and Peter Oliver (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Ononuja Family, June 1, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - OOLP, Feb. 24, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Oregon, University of, Library, Apr. 19, 1965-June 4, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Oshima Shotaro, Jan. 21-Sept. 20, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - O'Toole, Linda, and Tom Rurup, Feb.-Aug. 1986 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Overlook Press, Mar. 28-July 29, 1988, See also: Deborah Baker (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Owen, Lily, Dec. 1971-Apr. 1976 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Owle, Caledonia, June 28, 1970-Easter 1988 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Oxfam, 1983? (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Oxford University Press, Apr. 16, 1984-Mar. 9, 1987, See also: Athlone Press, and Kirkham, Michael (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Oxley, William, Aug. 3, 1982-Feb. 1983 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Pacifica Radio-WBAI, Jan. 10-Feb. 13, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Palm Beach Times, Jan. 20, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Palmer, Della, Jan. 26, 1973-Apr. 11, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Papers on Language and Literature, Oct. 4-Nov. 14, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Paris Review, Aug. 22, 1980-Aug. 13, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Parker, Maria Jackson, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Maria Jackson Parker (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Parnassus: Poetry in Review, Mar. 8, 1985-Nov. 14, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Patai, Daphne, May 14, 1983-Aug. 25, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Pauly, Thomas E., Aug. 18, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Pelican Island Audubon Society, 1980?-Oct. 3, 1986, See also: National Audubon Society (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - P.E.N (an international writers' association), Jan. 7, 1972-Sept. 4, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Pepin, Sherla, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Perkins, David, Feb. 25, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Pernu, Wynn, June 16, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Persea Books, July 20, 1979-Apr. 8, 1988, See also: Carcanet New Press (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Personalities of the South, American Biographical Institute, Oct. 10, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Phaups, Evelyn, Jan. 14-June 17, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Phillips, Jill, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Phoenix Book Shop, Oct. 26, 1980-Nov. 9, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Pierce, M., July 30, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Pino family, Dec. 20, 1966-May 29, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Pitt, Honor, Feb. 10, 1975-May 10, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - PN Review, See: Carcanet New Press (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Poetry, May 29, 1962-Dec. 1980 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Poets & Writers, Oct. 1, 1975-Mar. 17, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Portland Poetry Festival, Dec. 15, 1975-Jan. 31, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Potts, Louise, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Pratt, William, Aug. 30-Oct. 16, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Premru, Susan, June 22, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Preuss, Dan. Realtor, Aug. 5, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Princeton Alumni Weekly (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Princeton University (Box 27, Folder 3)
        - Alumni Association, Oct. 19, 1972-Aug. 28, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 3)
        - Annual Giving, June 9, 1969-June 1, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 3)
        - Class of '22, July 31, 1967-Aug. 6, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Princeton University Press, July 28, 1977-July 12, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Proof (University of South Carolina), May 22, 1973-Feb. 25, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Pugliese family, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Punch (London), July 5, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Putnam's Sons, See: Targ, William (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Quaker Oats Company, Oct. 19, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Raiziss, Sonia (Giop), See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Sonia Raiziss to Laura (Riding) Jackson and to Schuyler B. Jackson (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Randle, Pamela, Darrell, and Teresa Ann, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Random House, Dec. 12, 1961-Mar. 1, 1985, See also: Jerome Rothenberg and The Seabury Press (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Raritan: A Quarterly Review, July 2-July 28, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Rasula, Jed, Aug. 28-Nov. 29, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Rauch, Horst, July 29, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Reader's Digest, Mar. 9, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Reeves, James, All letters to/from Reeves formerly in Box 27, Folder 4 were moved to related collection #6304
      - Reichenthal, Nathaniel, Dec. 28, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Reichenthal, Robert (aka Robert Richey), See: Series III. Correspondence C)Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Robert Reichenthal (aka Robert Ritchey) See also: County of Los Angeles, Office of the Public Guardian (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Reichenthal, Sadie Edersheim [mother], Oct. 27, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Reprint House International, Jan. 13, 1971-July 27, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - The Review,Nov. 17, 1970-Aug. 4, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Reynard: The Magazine of the Quaker Fellowship of the Arts, Dec. 22, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Reynolds, Les and Eleonor, Dec. 1971-Dec. 1978 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Rhodes, Ida, Oct. 3-Oct. 10, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Richards, Jennifer, Apr. 10, 1981-Jan. 1987 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Rideal, Eric K. and Margaret, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Eric and Margaret Rideal (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Riding, Peter, Oct. 4, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Rivera, Leslie, May 4, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Roach, Mary, Dec. 1963-Dec. 1965 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Roberts, Eyrlis with Jacob Bronowski, May 12, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Robison, Alan, Feb. 7, 1986-Nov. 3, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Rodell, Marie, June 12-Aug. 19, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Rodgers, Bethy, Nov. 12, 1981-Feb. 14, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Rohen, Ernest, Mar. 1970-Apr. 1979 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Rose, Edward L., Aug. 20, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Rosenthal, M. L., Aug. 6, 1977-Dec. 24, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Rothenberg, Jerome, Sept. 6, 1972-Dec. 13, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - The Mark Rothko Foundation, June 23, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Routledge & Kegan Paul, Feb. 9, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Rubenstein, Meyer Raphael, Dec. 3, 1979-Jan. 9, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Ruffur, James, Dec. 1, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Rurup, Thomas, Feb. 26,-Mar. 5, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Russell & Volkening, Oct. 26, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Ruzicka, Ivan J. and Jirina, Dec. 9, 1969-Mar. 7, 1976, See also: related collection # 4665 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Ruzicka, Ivan J. and Jirina [includes ms. sent to Ivan Ruzicka by L(R)J ca. August 1975], Mar. 25, 1976-Oct. 19, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Ryall, Christine, Aug. 24, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Salas, Randall, Dec. 29, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Salty Sparks Co., Realtors, Aug. 25, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Sanazaro, Leonard, July 3, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - San Diego, University of California at, July 9, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Sartain, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Saturday Review, June 15, 1966-ca. May 1971 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Nathan N. Schildkraut [includes a letter from Schildkraut to Robert Graves, Feb. 23, 1940, with a draft of Laura Riding's response; the unsigned carbon of the reply from Robert Graves, Mar. 19, 1940; and a letter in Spanish, written and signed by Laura Riding, Sept. 30, 1940] (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Schmidt, Ella [Mrs. Gustav], Sept. 8, 1968-Jan. 1981 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Schmidt, Michael (as editor of PN Review), See: Carcanet New Press (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Scholarly Press, Feb. 23-Sept. 30, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Schulson, David, Sept. 20, 1978-June 9, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Seabold, Russ and Jane, Dec. 1975-Dec. 1978 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Seabury Press, Apr. 26, 1974-Feb. 20, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Sears, Roebuck, and Co., Sept. 5, 1975-Feb. 7, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Seaton, Peter, Apr. 7-June 19, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Sebastian Volunteer Fire Department and Ambulance Squad, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Martin Secker & Warburg, July 21, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Secretary of State. Home Office (U.K.), Sept. 6-Apr. 14, 1928 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Seluzicki, Charles, July 17, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Sepp, Anto, Jan. 2, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Serendipity Books, Aug. 5, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Sewanee Review, Oct. 15-Nov. 18, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Seymour-Smith, Martin and Janet, Oct. 21, 1964-Feb. 5, 1965, See also: Nye, Robert (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Shapiro, David, Feb. 1, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Sharpe, David, Jan. 30, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Anthony Sheil Associates, May 17, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Shenandoah: The Washington and Lee University Review, Aug. 10, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Sherley, Nellie B., Aug. 16, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Sherwin, Judith Johnson, Jan. 21-Feb. 25, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Simon, Marc, Nov. 8, 1976-Oct. 24, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Simon-Ross, Celia, Sept. 2, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Simoneau, Peter, Aug. 23-Sept. 26, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Sisterhood, July 26, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Skulski, Kenneth, Oct. 6, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Slater, Jean, Sept. 15, 1969-Jan. 14, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Smith, Dorothy, Summer 1972-July 1982 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Smith, Florence, Aug. 19, 1971-Dec. 1975 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Smith, Grace, 1971-1987 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Smith, Loretta, May 1971-June? 1974 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Smith, Mabel P., Aug. 27, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Smith, Peter, June 2, 1970-June 29, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Snyder, Clara and Jessie, July 17, 1951-May 13, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Snyder, Clara and Jessie [cont.], May 18, 1971-June 19, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Somerset House, Apr. 15, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Somerville, Maisie, July 22-Aug. 8, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Sophomore Literary Festival, See: University of Notre Dame (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Sormani, Egbert J., Oct. 2, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - South Central Review: The Journal of the South Central Modern Language Association, Aug. 29, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Southern Illinois University at Carbondale. Morris Library, June 10, 1969-Mar. 23, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Sparrow, John, Feb 5-Mar. 27, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Spiegel, Mrs. Otto [Sadie], Feb. 26, 1963-Feb. 8, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - State University of New York College at New Palts, June 12, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Stein, Diana, Jan. 24, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Stein, Gertrude, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Gertrude Stein (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Steven, Christopher, Feb. 19, 1976-June 1, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Sternberg, Linda, and Bill Katz, Sept. 11-Dec. 29, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - St. Johns River Water Management District (Florida), July 3-Sept. 16, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - St. Martin's Press, Apr. 16, 1976-June 1980 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - St. Petersburg Airport, Dec. 4, 1967-July 2, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Stockwhip, Burwood, Mar. 14, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Stokes, Daniel, and Leesa, Sept. 14, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Stone, Catherine, Aug. 27, 1968-Jan. 1980 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - C. A. Stonehill, July 17-July 28, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Stough, Roy, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Stoute, Henrik, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Studies in Philology (University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill), July 10, 1975-Aug. 27, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Stull, Edna and Bain, Oct. 24, 1966-Oct. 29, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Stull, Edna and Bain [cont.], June 14, 1974-July 8, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Sturgeon, Tandy, Apr. 12, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Sugg, Redding S., Mar. 14, 1973-Nov. 8, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Sulfur, May 12, 1983-Dec. 3, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Sullivan, Nora, Aug. 3, 1973-Dec. 1977 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Summerall, Albert, Helen, and Vickie, ca. 1978 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Sun & Moon Press, Jan. 8, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Sunday Telegraph, Aug. 11, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Surratt, Jerl, Oct. 17, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Sutherland, Donald, Nov. 15, 1973-May 6, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Sutherland, John, Aug. 13, 1969-Dec. 21, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Sutton, Dovie, ca. 1963 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Syracuse University, Aug. 5, 1963-July 24, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Szladits, Lola, Dec. 25, 1980-Nov. 10, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Targ, William, Sept. 19, 1975-Mar. 9, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - La Tartaruga, Jan. 29, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Tate, Allen, See: "The Absolute of Poetry" ts. 12pp. carbon [by Allen Tate?] in Series IX. Writings by others (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Terzian, Michael, Sept. 28, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Testerman, Tim, Nov. 25, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Texaco, Nov. 8, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Texas, University of. Humanities Research Center, Dec. 17, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Thames Polytechnic, Sept. 25, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Thigpen, Walter, Jan. 3, 1968-Dec. 19, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Thigpen, Walter [cont.], Jan. 5, 1969-Jan. 26, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - 35's Women's Campaign for Soviet Jewry, Sept. 30, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Thompson, Elizabeth, July 8, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Thorn, Fred, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Thornton, Roger, July 21, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Thurman, Mary, June 2, 1972--June 5, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Tiers, Lowber, July 1977-July 2, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Time, Apr. 5, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - The Times, Oct. 1, 1980-Aug. 30, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - The Times Higher Education Supplement, Apr. 26, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Times Literary Supplement, Nov. 1, 1971-June 14, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Tingey, William, Sept. 23, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Tolley, A. T. [Trevor], May 29, 1972-Jan. 22, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Travers, Pamela, Aug. 15, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Trotman, Michael, Apr. 14, 1986-Feb. 9, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Truesdale, C. W., Jan. 13-Mar. 23, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Tuckwell, Patience, Nov. 29-Dec. 14, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Tulsa, University of, Sept. 14, 1976-Jan. 10, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Tulsa World, See: Thompson, Elizabeth (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Tyler, James, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, James Tyler (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Underwood, Thomas A., May 10-June 16, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - United States Mission to the United Nations, Nov. 21, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - United States Postal Service. Orlando, Florida, July 25, 1979-Feb. 20, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - University Microfilms International, Sept. 6, 1968-Mar. 1989, See also: Xerox University Microfilms (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - University of California at Davis. Department of English., See: Hoffman, Michael (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - University of Chicago Press, Sept. 16, 1969-May 5, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - University of Georgia Press, Sept. 10, 1971-Apr. 25, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - University of Nebraska Press, May 22, 1974, See also: Sutherland, Donald (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - University of Notre Dame, July 9, 1976-Sept. 4, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - University of Tennessee Press, Nov. 18-Dec. 10, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - University of Toronto Quarterly, Feb. 10, 1977-Feb. 8, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - University Place Book Shop, Nov. 26, 1968, Aug. 20, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Untamed Shrew, Nov. 18, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Vanderbilt University Library, July 1, 1952-Sept. 14, 1981, See also: Nashville, Tennessee. Joint University Libraries (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - VanDeVoorde, René G., Sept. 4, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Van Dore, Wade, May 1, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Vero Beach Monument Service, Dec. 4, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Vice, John, July 1, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Victoria, University of. Special Collections, Feb. 15, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Viking Press, Nov. 24, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Villa, José Garcia, Dec. 11, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Virago Limited, July 30-Aug. 30, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - [Virginia], Apr. 4, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Virginia Quarterly Review, Jan. 18-Feb. 28, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Vives, 1936? (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Vuckovic, Jovica, Sept. 2-Sept. 22, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Wabasso, Florida. Postal Office, Jan. 1984, Jan. 1987 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Waldron, Ann, Feb. 1, 1985-Feb. 2, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Walker, Eva, Jan. 16, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Ward, Don Reynolds, May 7, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Ward, Robert, July 9, 1974-Jan. 2, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Wasson, John and Bennie, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Watkins, Alison, May-June 1983 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Watkins, Armitage, June 12-19, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Watson, Audrey, Jan. 5, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Watson, George, Sept. 29, 1976-Feb. 4, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Watson-Gutpill Publications, Mar. 17, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - A. P. Watt & Son, June 8, 1943-Sept. 18, 1968, See also: Carcanet New Press (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - A. P. Watt & Son [cont.], Oct. 7, 1968-July 18, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Weiss, Jordan, Mar. 1982 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Wesleyan University Press, June 2, 1966-Mar. 6, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - West, Rebecca, May 30-July 4, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Wexler, Joyce, June 28, 1971-Aug. 24, 1972., See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Joyce Wexler (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Wexler, Joyce [cont.] [includes Hynes, Samuel, Apr. 24, 1973-June 5, 1977], Sept. 9, 1972-Jan. 27, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Wheelhouse, Frances, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Whelen, Christopher, Sept. 29-Nov. 16, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Whitmire, Carolyn, 1974? (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Who's Who in America, Sept. 8, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Whyte, Hamish, Feb. 25, 1982-July 23, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Wieland, Albert, Feb. 26, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Wier, Dara, Feb. 23-Mar. 19, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Wigfield, Virginia, 1965?-July 10, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Wiggins, Jim, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Wilentz, Joan, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Joan and Theodore Wilentz (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Wilentz, Theodore, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Joan and Theodore Wilentz (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Willet, Henry, Sept. 15, 1982-Nov. 1983, See also: Princeton University. Class of '22 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Williams, Mary, July 6?-Sept. 5,[1985] (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Wilson, Barbara, Apr. 11-Apr. 30, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - H. W. Wilson Company, Feb. 8-Apr. 13, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Wilson, Floreide, ca. 1972-Dec. 14, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Wilson, Paul A., ca. 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Wimsatt, W.K., Aug. 6 and 27, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Winter Beach Cemetery Association, July 29, 1968-Oct. 21, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Winterkorn, Joan, Jan. 24, 1979-Aug. 28, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Wintermill, Betty and Charlie, Dec. 1974 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Wood, David, Sept. 20, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Woods, Marion, Aug. 27, 1968-Feb. 28, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - J. Howard Woolmer Books, Aug. 21, 1973-July 27, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - J. Howard Woolmer Books [cont.], Aug. 13, 1976-July 19, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Woolmer & Brotherson, Jan. 16, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Stuart Wright Publisher, 1984? (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Wyatt, [Ellidge], Honor and Robert, Apr. 2-June 22, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Wyoming, University of. Division of Rare Books and Special Collections, Sept. 15, 1971-Mar. 6, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Xerox University Microfilms, Apr. 19-Aug. 13 1976, See also: University Microfilms International (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Yale University Library. Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Jan. 2, 1975-Feb. 11, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Yale University Press, Sept. 16, 1976-Oct. 6, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Yeargin, Desiree and Willie, Dec. 1978 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Yellin, Herb, Feb. 11, 1981-Mar. 15, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Yoken, Melvin B., June 26, 1970-May 9, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Ziegfield, Richard, Jan. 28, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Outgoing
      - undated correspondence (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - outgoing correspondence, 1932-Jan. 1933 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - [first letter, unsigned, is by Robert Graves, Feb. 1, 1933] (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Mar.-May. 1933 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - [includes "I was born in New York City...", ms. enclosed with letter to Living Authors, Jul. 4, 1933], May-Dec. 1933 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - [includes letter by Robert Graves to New Verse, June 23, 1934, with enclosure], Jan.-July 1934 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - 1935-1944, [includes letter of July 18, 1935 from "John" to "Mary"] (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Dec. 1945-May 1962 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - July 1962-Feb. 1963 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Mar. 1963-Oct. 1964 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Nov. 1964-June 1965 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - July-Dec. 1965 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Jan.-Jun. 1966 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - July 1966-Dec. 1967 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Jan.-May 1968 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - June-Oct. 1968 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Nov.-Dec. 1968 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Jan.-Feb. 1969 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Mar.-Apr. 1969 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - May.-June 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - July-Sept. 1969 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Oct.-Dec. 1969 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Jan.-Mar. 1970 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Apr. 1970 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - May 1970 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - June 1970 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - July 1970 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Aug. 1970 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Sept. 1970 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Oct. 1970 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Nov.-Dec. 1970 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Jan.-Feb. 1971 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Mar.-Apr. 1971 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - May.-June 1971 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - July-Aug. 1971 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Sept.-Aug.1971 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Nov.-Dec. 1971 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Jan.-Feb. 1972 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Mar.-Apr. 1972 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - May-June 1972 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - July-Aug. 1972 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Sept. 1972 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Oct. 1972 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Nov. 1972 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Dec. 1972-Jan. 1973 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Feb.-Mar. 1973 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Apr.-May 1973 (Box 39, Folder 4)